It's my life.
It's your life.
Fighting for tomorrow.
Go get what you really want.
I want more. Anyone more.
Come on, open up the door.
It's my life. It's your life.
Run like a wind, jump high.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Believe you can achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going on the stage.
Let's do it again, you
know what I mean, baby.
No one can make my dream come true!
Don't you feel it?
I really don't know what is
Something is testing me every day.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away.
I know I never wanna come back here.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away. The great
end of the unknown rules.
Standing up, blowing up.
My dream is getting wilder.
I'm not afraid, beat me, hit me.
I will never turn around.
Another day, another chance.
You know it's never too late.
If I can't do it, so
can you. Only without.
It's my life, it's your life.
Party for tomorrow. Go
get what you really want.
I want more, anyone more,
come on, open up the door.
It's my life. It's your life.
Run like a wind, jump high, yeah, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Believe you cannot achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going, roaring.
It's my life, it's your life.
Fighting for your eyes that
I want, but your weary ones.
I want more, anyone more,
come on, open up the gate.
It's my life. It's your light.
Shine like a star to be good.
I know you're strong. Just that
you can't achieve your best.
Let's keep on going. Out of day.
You make my day every day.
No! This way!
We've got to get to the
center of town! Keep going!
Those buildings are getting
dragged across the ground!
And they're coming straight for us! Run!
The kingdom's getting crushed into a ball!
And us along with it!
The birdcage is shrinking.
That would explain the mass panic.
The birdcage buries everything.
Honey, this is a nightmare!
I see the battle isn't over yet.
I found honey again.
This is really happening.
I'm not gonna sit here picking my
nose waiting for death to come.
Go find our fallen
allies—get them back up.
All right.
If
the battle goes on for too long, even
this plateau will be cut to pieces.
What
I thought this was the middle
of the kingdom isn't it?
The safest place?
Look above.
The
center is slowly moving too, huh?
It's probably closing in on
the royal palace on top of the.
the
plateau.
In other words, where Doflamingo
is fighting right now.
Unless we push toward the center,
we'll be shredded like everything else.
Now that we're in the midst of it,
I see that things are quite chaotic.
This way.
Cesaro!
Might I inquire where
you're going, Sir Zoro?
What do you mean?
Isn't it obvious?
Huh?
We're going to stop that thing.
There.
Where?
No!
What a surprise.
I never knew there were little
people here in Dressrosa.
I hope your arm turns out all right.
They said it should be back in working
order once the blood flow returns.
Yeah, I know.
I'm a doctor.
When I saw that underground
port, one thing became clear.
This is much bigger than one man.
Even if we defeat Doflamingo,
the battle won't be over.
But it will cause
ripples across the world.
And all eyes will be on you and Straw Hat.
Yeah, that was the plan.
4th gear, do tell.
That's right.
I gotta kick your ass in a hurry.
It's nothing like second.
Oh, yeah!
Bounce man!
I'm sorry, is this supposed to be a joke?
You certainly got big.
I'll give you that much.
Do you think a balloon scares me?
And here I thought you had some
secret strategy to win this.
What are you going to do?
Bounce me to death?
You can't even stand on
your own two feet anymore.
How are you supposed to kick my
ass with a stupid power like that?
For two whole years, I
fought against wild animals.
As huge and savage as any
monster you could think of.
If I wanted to wrestle them to the ground,
I needed greater size
and greater bounciness.
And what good does elasticity do?
Shut up!
Once I start, you won't
even be able to fight back!
Now my Gum-Gum!
Come!
Die!
It's Doflamingo!
Everyone stand back.
Don't move. What the hell?
are you doing here i'd
like to know that myself
Hello?
We'll end up hitting the breadcrumbs!
This is downtown.
It really knocked me a long way.
It's using elastic force to fly?
This one's my Gum-Gum!
Rhino Schneider!
Somebody else showed up!
He's massive!
And it looks like he's strong, too!
He's a... giant... ball man?
Little bastard.
He's hardening his skin with
armament Haki and using the
tensile force to multiply his
strength several times over.
I'm not gonna lose to a ball.
I'm stronger than rubber.
I'm so sick of this crap!
I told you, didn't I?
Now that I'm using 4th
gear, you can't keep up!
Here I come, Mingo!
Who the hell do you think
you're dealing with?
Now, Gum-Gum!
To the red!
Athlete!
Even with the armor,
he's still like rubber.
You think that's going to work on me?
Not now!
Yeah.
I can't believe this.
Don't you dare try and run away.
You're going to get that ass kicking.
What's happening?
It keeps going.
Chase him down. Python!
Damn it.
How far can his arm stretch?
Ahh!
Enough! Teach this!
And now comes on!
Culverin!
He got a beating! Doflamingo?
From a ball? How?
Hang on, who's that? He's strong. Wow.
Knock him dead!
You can do it!
Straw Hat? Yeah.
He's so different now.
Is that him?
I mean, it's hard to believe.
Why, if he can overpower
Doflamingo, he must be quite strong.
But...
he's overusing his Haki.
Oh, dear. Really?
Ah, there he is.
Guess they're playing somewhere else now.
And after I went to all that trouble
to come over here and see them!
The captain of the first ship of the
Blackbeard Pirates, Jesus Burgess.
Looks like I found him. Chase them?
Or wait?
Either way, they're mine for sure.
I'll get what I want, no matter what!
Wee!
I was right.
He's after Luffy's group.
But what's his motive?
Viola.
His fight with Luffy is
all that remains, correct?
That's right, Father.
All of the top executives and their
underlings have been eliminated.
Only Doflamingo remains.
Let's move, Tontanus!
Hurry it up!
We're on our way!
Step up, or else you guys are
gonna be super dead in a minute!
We managed to rescue all our friends
who were stranded in the factory.
We're good to go!
Sweet!
Hey, the building's leaning over!
Froland, why is the Smile Factory the
only thing that's not getting cut off?
Wait, it's not?
Right, the Sea Prism Stone.
Sea Prism?
Yeah, that's what the
walls are made out of.
It's pretty strong stuff.
Which means, the strings cut everything
else, but the factory won't crack.
Here, watch. Huh?
We're just pushing it.
Hey, it's them! Cranky!
Ah! Sir Robot!
Saru Land. Top that land!
Uh, guys, what gives?
Center of the country is kind
of in the other direction.
Want to run? Turn around.
What?
We're not running.
We want to stop the strings.
Stop them?
I didn't even think about that. Wow!
That's amazing!
It's not over until Luffy settles
the score, but we can buy some time.
Oh, yeah!
Even with his armament active, he can still
expand and contract with such precision.
Armament and rubber
working in harmony, huh?
If I take too long, I'll change back!
It seems like you've figured out
how to use that ability pretty well.
But it must take a toll
on you after a while.
I'm sure it has its risks.
You're tired, aren't you?
How long can you hold out?
You know...
I can use my strings as much as I'd like.
Culverin!
Off what?
The ground?
How did you do that?
Master, what have you done to this town?
Listen closely, rookie.
My Devil Fruit's power ascended.
They've reached a new horizon.
A higher state known as Awakening.
Whoa!
He turns the buildings into strings!
Awakening is extremely rare.
But with it, my strings can
affect more than just my own body.
Dear!
His strings are all over the place!
This can't be a parameathia!
No matter which way you go,
there's more strings. Fun, right?
At this rate, you won't
even be able to get near me.
Tick-tock.
Any minute now, your
body's going to give out.
And mine will keep on going.
You won't quit.
Hockey's about to run out. Straw Hat.
That's when I'll deliver
the finishing blow!
We have to run, or let's just pop!
Oh no, Grandma!
I thought I'd stand up
for you and make it!
I'm sorry.
I can't run anymore.
Leave me and save yourself, dear.
I won't do that!
I'm not going to abandon you!
Hurry, run.
This is the end for me either way.
Come on, get up!
I'm telling you, I don't have
enough strength to run downtown.
You should go quickly.
People!
We need help here!
All these patients, they can't get out!
And we can't carry them by ourselves!
I've lost my son!
He's wearing a Kuma shirt!
Have you seen him?
Please, no!
There must be someone who
can help me find my baby!
Everybody's gonna die no matter what.
It's pointless.
Even if we run you're stuck in the cage.
Doflamingo will kill us anyway,
so it's easier to just give up.
Please, listen well.
It is on.
King, rather, former king, Rick Dolgo III.
What's going on?
It's really him?
As you can see, yes.
Because of the game that the current
King Doflamingo has forced upon us,
We've been trapped inside this
birdcage with seemingly no escape.
And, to make matters even more
bleak, the cage is rapidly shrinking,
slicing everything in sight.
Rick...
This was thrust upon you so suddenly.
I'm sure your emotions
could barely keep up,
and now you struggle to survive
and protect your loved ones.
This may feel like a
nightmare, but it's quite real,
and this tragedy did not just begin today,
because for a whole decade,
Dressrosa was already a birdcage,
and all of us were being held inside,
under the oppressive reign of pirates.
For ten years now we have been puppets,
constantly being manipulated
by the strings that they
pulled.
Such has been our reality.
But soon that is going to change.
The fear Don Quixote family,
whom we believe were unstoppable,
have nearly been eliminated
by a group of mighty warriors
who only happen to be
passing through our country.
None of the executives are
left standing. Oh, really?
Who could do that?
I don't know, but it wasn't us.
The final obstacle is him.
The ruthless tyrant who has
Cheshrosa under his thumb.
Do Flamingo.
And the brave soul who is doing battle
with him is Luffy of the Straw Hat Pirates.
I believe he'll save us.
He'll destroy this
birdcage once and for all.
That win or lose, it
will end in mere minutes.
So try to survive until then,
no matter what it takes.
Our dear country may be crumbling, but
I cannot allow you to go down with it.
I implore you to keep running.
Even if you run out of breath
or your legs are broken.
For a few minutes, please try to survive.
There is still hope for us.
That is why you mustn't surrender yet.
We'll do our best alone.
Right. Good.
Let's go! Run!
Okay!
Yeah.
You should do what King Rick says.
Don't give up.
Let's all run downtown together.
Help the patients!
Grab the beds!
Here.
Mummy!
We have to survive
until the battle's over!
That Straw Hat pirate is going to put
Doflamingo in his place! I know it! Yeah!
I said Bingo!
Your demise is long overdue.
There's not much time left.
The whole town's starting to strike.
Now billow white.
It's over.
I'll blow you away!
You're mine now!
I'm going to end this for good!
With my Gum-Gum!
Leo Bazooka!
He won.
He beat the flamingo!